

■ balinta.dev@gmail.com

+36 20 451 2353

Budapest, Hungary

in linkedin.com/in/balinta

ABOUT

a customer-first With approach and over ten years of development experience, including web applications, client-server systems and databases, I'm keen on finding the best possible solution to any problems. I have a strong desire to maintain high professional standards and to continuously challenge myself to further expand my technical knowledge.

KEY SKILLS

TECHNOLOGIES

.NET 5, 6, 7, 8 .NET Framework ASP.NET Core Web API, MVC RESTful Web Services Docker, Kubernetes LINQ, Entity Framework

LANGUAGES

C#, SQL, JavaScript HTML, CSS, JSON, XML

IDE & Tools

Visual Studio, VS Code ReSharper, Postman

ATTILA BALINT

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

JUL 2023 - CURRENT

BETSSON GROUP

BUDAPEST, HU

Skills & Technologies: Backend heavy full-stack development and maintenance • C#, MS SQL, JavaScript • ASP.NET Core, REST, WCF, .NET 7.0 and 8.0 • Docker, Kubernetes, Redis, Amazon S3 • Octopus, TeamCity, GitHub Actions • Monitoring with Grafana, Prometheus, Jaeger • Postman, SoapUI • JIRA issue tracking • Code reviews, source control and release management

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

SEP 2021 - CURRENT

TOPTAL

REMOTE

Skills & Technologies: Full-stack development and maintenance • C#, SQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap • ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core MVC and Web API, .NET 5.0 and 6.0 • Swagger, Postman • SOLID coding principles • Docker containers • SAP Business One SDK with DI API, Crystal Reports SDK • Azure DevOps • Third-party API integration and data transfer automation, Zapier

SENIOR DEVELOPER

JUN 2020 - FEB 2021

KPMG GLOBAL SERVICES HUNGARY

BUDAPEST, HU

Key Responsibilities: Participate as a full-stack developer in service design, development and delivery • Support an extremely growing business with efficient software solutions • Improve performance and productivity of existing applications • Collaborate with the whole development team in building various new solutions and applications

Skills & Technologies: Full-stack development • C#, SQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS • Design patterns and SOLID coding principles • ASP.NET and ASP.NET Core 3.1 Web API and MVC • Azure DevOps, Agile practices • Code reviews and source control management

APPLICATION MAINTENANCE DEVELOPERKPMG UK

JUL 2018 - APR 2020

MANCHESTER, UK

Key Responsibilities: Pick up and understand new technologies quickly • Analyze, develop and modify a wide range of applications • Follow best development practices to ensure clean code and high-quality products • Provide technical support • Estimate and implement change requests, meet deadlines • Investigate and resolve issues

Skills & Technologies: Full-stack development • C#, T-SQL, HTML, JavaScript, basic React/Redux experience • SOLID design principles • ASP.NET Web API and MVC, Web Forms, WPF • Azure DevOps, Kanban, Agile practices • CI/CD using Git, TeamCity and Octopus • OpenID Connect authentication • Azure AD B2C • Microsoft Azure services • Power BI Embedded reports integration

MORE SKILLS

DATABASE

MS SQL Server SSMS, T-SQL

CLOUD SERVICES

AWS, Microsoft Azure

MONITORING

Grafana, Prometheus, Jaeger OpenTelemetry

SOURCE CONTROL

Git, GitHub Actions, GitFlow

UNIT TESTING

NUnit, xUnit, MSTest

CI/CD TOOLS

TeamCity, Octopus
Azure DevOps (VSTS)

METHODOLOGIES

Agile, Kanban, Scrum

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

professional proficiency

HUNGARIAN

native speaker

GERMAN

elementary proficiency

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF
ENGINEERING IN
SOFTWARE INFORMATION
TECHNOLOGY

University of Pannonia, 2012 Veszprem, HU

Field of Study: Computer Science and Programming

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

JUL 2016 - JUN 2018

PRODUMEX

BUDAPEST, HU

Key Responsibilities: Performance enhancement, code optimization • Debug applications, identify and resolve issues • Translate business requirements into code • Understand and customize various business processes • Provide technical support

Skills & Technologies: .NET, C#, T-SQL, XML development • Extensive experience of SAP B1 SDK • RESTful web services using JSON • Basic experience in Xamarin Android • Coding mobile client applications • Working with Git and SVN • Planning and issue tracking using JIRA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

May 2013 - Jun 2017

BX Software - Variatech Consulting

BUDAPEST, HU

Key Responsibilities: Developing a new SAP B1 integrated mobile warehouse system • Estimating and implementing function requests • Identifying, tracking and fixing bugs • Creating and running automated test scripts to support application testing

Skills & Technologies: SAP Business One add-on development, C#, T-SQL • Extensive experience of Microsoft technologies, including WinForms, ASP.NET Web API, Visual Studio, MS SQL Server and stored procedures • Git version control

KEY PROJECTS

HEALTHCARE PLATFORM INTEGRATION AND AUTOMATION

The project involved integrating and automating specific aspects of a healthcare web platform with third-party vendors to enhance the efficiency and reliability of data transfers. I worked on this project as a full-stack developer using C#, ASP.NET MVC and Web API, Microsoft SQL Server, Zapier, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Azure DevOps, and IIS.

VAT COMPLIANCE PORTAL MAINTENANCE AND DEVELOPMENT

The project aimed to improve the performance and productivity of an existing web portal and add new features to comply with the latest business regulations. I was a full-stack developer working on web application maintenance and implementing changes using C#, ASP.NET, SQL Server, Azure DevOps, IIS, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.

WAREHOUSE MANAGEMENT SOLUTION FOR SAP BUSINESS ONE

An integrated warehouse management solution for real-time SAP Business One transactions. I worked on this product as a full-stack developer using WinForms with the .NET Compact Framework for handheld devices, C#, ASP.NET Web API, SAP Business One SDK including DI API and UI API, and Microsoft SQL Server on the back-end.